<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<strings>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGDesert">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 100 rounds of JHP ammunition, 100 rounds of FMJ ammunition, cleaning kit, small weapon case, holster with attachment pack to store magazines. Place of Origin: Magnum Research Inc - Minnesota, USA.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGNighthawk">Premium .45 1911-Derivate. The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 100 rounds of JHP ammunition, 100 rounds of FMJ ammunition, cleaning kit, small weapon case, suppressor, laser sight, flashlight, pistol red dot sight, holster with attachment pack to store magaziness. Place of Origin: Yonkers, New York, USA.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGGyurza">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 100 rounds of SP-10 ammunition, 100 rounds of SP-11 ammunition, cleaning kit, small weapon case, holster with attachment pack to store magazines. Place of Origin: TSNIITOCHMASH - Klimovsk, Russia.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGGlock22">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 100 rounds of JHP ammunition, 100 rounds of FMJ ammunition, cleaning kit, small weapon case, laser sight, flashlight, threaded barrel, suppressor, pistol red dot sight, holster with attachment pack to store magazines. Place of Origin: GLOCK USA - Georgia, USA.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGCZ75Shadow">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 100 rounds of JHP ammunition, 100 rounds of FMJ ammunition, cleaning kit, small weapon case, laser sight, flashlight, suppressor, pistol red dot sight, holster with attachment pack to store magazines. Place of Origin: CZ-USA - Kansas, USA.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGPT1911">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 100 rounds of JHP ammunition, 100 rounds of FMJ ammunition, cleaning kit, small weapon case, suppressor, laser sight, flashlight, pistol red dot sight, holster with attachment pack to store magaziness. Place of Origin: Forjas Taurus S.A. - Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGUSPMATCH">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 100 rounds of JHP ammunition, 100 rounds of FMJ ammunition, cleaning kit, small weapon case, laser sight, flashlight, pistol red dot sight, holster with attachment pack to store magaziness. Place of Origin: Heckler & Koch USA - Georgia, USA.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG90Two">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 100 rounds of JHP ammunition, 100 rounds of FMJ ammunition, cleaning kit, small weapon case, suppressor, laser sight, flashlight, pistol red dot sight, holster with attachment pack to store magaziness. Place of Origin: Beretta USA - Maryland, USA.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG57">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 100 rounds of JHP ammunition, 100 rounds of FMJ ammunition, cleaning kit, small weapon case, suppressor, laser sight, flashlight, pistol red dot sight, holster with attachment pack to store magaziness. Place of Origin: FN America - Virginia, USA.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG007">If you ever wanted to feel like everybody's favorite 00-Agent, look no further. Package includes a Walther PPK with everything a Secret Agent needs plus a Special Edition Gold Lighter. Laser Watch not included. Place of Origin: Bobby Ray's Guns and Things.</str>
	
	<!-- SHOTGUNS -->
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGKSG">Keltec's groundbreaking 12 Gauge Shotgun, the Package includes Case, AN/PEQ-2 for Target Illumination, Aimpoint T-1 Micro RDS, Manual, Cleaning Kit, 20 armor-piercing Sabot-Shells and 30 N4 Shotgun-Shells. Place of Origin: Cocoa, Florida, USA.</str>
	
	<!-- SMGS -->

	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGMP510MM">We're at Bobby Ray's are proud to deliver a MP5-10mm to you which in no ways is inferior to the FBI issued ones. Package includes four 10mm Magazines, 90 Rounds JHP-Ammo, Silencer, RIS Body Kit, Folding Stock, Surefire Flashlight Foregrip, Barska Red Dot Sight, Medium Transportation Case and Cleaning Kit. Detailed Manual comes along. Place of Origin: Bobby Ray's Guns and Things.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGMP9">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of FMJ ammunition, suppressor, red dot sight, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Brugger & Thomet AG - Thun, Bern, Switzerland.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGMX4">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of FMJ ammunition, suppressor, red dot sight, tactical foregrip, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Fabbrica d'Armi Pietro Beretta - Brescia, Italy.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGBIZON9x18">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 350 rounds of FMJ ammunition, suppressor, red dot sight, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Kalashnikov Concern / IZHMASH - Izhevsk, Udmurtia, Russia.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGBIZON9mm">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 272 rounds of +P+ ammunition, suppressor, red dot sight, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Kalashnikov Concern / IZHMASH - Izhevsk, Udmurtia, Russia.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGVityaz9mm">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 170 rounds of +P+ ammunition, suppressor, red dot sight, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Kalashnikov Concern / IZHMASH - Izhevsk, Udmurtia, Russia.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGFAMAESAF">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of FMJ ammunition, suppressor, red dot sight, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: FAMAE (Fabricas y Maestranzas del Ejercito) - Santiago, Chile.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGMT40">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of FMJ ammunition, suppressor, red dot sight, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Forjas Taurus S.A. - Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGMT40G2">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of FMJ ammunition, suppressor, red dot sight, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Forjas Taurus S.A. - Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil.</str>
	
	<!-- RIFLES -->
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSL8">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of Match ammunition, suppressor, laser sight, 4x ACOG scope, cleaning kit, user manual and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Heckler & Koch GmbH - Oberndorf am Neckar, Germany.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGHK33">The kit consists of 3 30 round spare magazines, 2 40 round spare magazines, 150 rounds of Match ammunition, suppressor, laser sight, sight mount, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Heckler & Koch GmbH - Oberndorf am Neckar, Germany.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGG41">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of Match ammunition, suppressor, laser sight, sight mount, fixed and telescopic stock, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Heckler & Koch GmbH - Oberndorf am Neckar, Germany.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGAK5CAR">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, suppressor, laser sight, red dot sight, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Saab Bofors Dynamics - Linkoping, Sweden.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGAK5">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, suppressor, laser sight, red dot sight, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Saab Bofors Dynamics - Linkoping, Sweden.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGAR70">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, suppressor, sight mount, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Fabbrica d'Armi Pietro Beretta - Brescia, Italy.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGAR7090">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, suppressor, sight mount, red dot sight, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Fabbrica d'Armi Pietro Beretta - Brescia, Italy.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGARX160">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, suppressor, red dot sight, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Fabbrica d'Armi Pietro Beretta - Brescia, Italy.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGFAMAS">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Nexter Systems - Roanne, France.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGFNC">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Fabrique Nationale d'Herstal - Herstal, Belgium.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSCARL">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, grenade launcher, 6 HE grenades, laser sight, red dot sight, tactical foregrip, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Fabrique Nationale d'Herstal - Herstal, Belgium.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSCARH">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 120 rounds of JHP ammunition, grenade launcher, 6 HE grenades, laser sight, red dot sight, tactical foregrip, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Fabrique Nationale d'Herstal - Herstal, Belgium.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGF2000">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, red dot sight, grenade launcher, 6 HE grenades, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Fabrique Nationale d'Herstal - Herstal, Belgium.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSS2">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: PT Pindad - Bandung, Indonesia.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGK2">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Daewoo Precision Industries - Busan, South Korea.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGTAURUSCT">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of FMJ ammunition, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Forjas Taurus S.A. - Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGBADGER">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, red dot sight, tactical foregrip, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Advanced Armament Corporation - Huntsville, Alabama.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGRK62">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, grenade launcher, 6 HE grenades, sight mount, bayonet, red dot sight, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: SAKO, Limited - Riihimaki, Finland.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGRK95">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, grenade launcher, 6 HE grenades, sight mount, bayonet, red dot sight, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: SAKO, Limited - Riihimaki, Finland.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGAK107">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, grenade launcher, 6 HE grenades, sight mount, bayonet, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Kalashnikov Concern - Izhevsk, Russia</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGM21">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Zastava Arms - Kragujevac, Serbia.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGM77">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 120 rounds of FMJ ammunition, suppressor, sight mount, red dot sight, bayonet, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Zastava Arms - Kragujevac, Serbia.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGVZ58">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, suppressor, bayonet, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of origin: Ceska zbrojovka a.s. - Uhersky Brod, Czech Republic.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSR3M">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of FMJ ammunition, suppressor, cleaning kit and magazine pouch. Place of Origin: TSNIITOCHMASH - Klimovsk, Russia.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSG542">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 120 rounds of JHP ammunition, cleaning kit, suppressor, bayonet, user manual and magazine pouch. Place of origin: FAMAE (Fabricas y Maestranzas del Ejercito) - Santiago, Chile.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSG550">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, a C-MORE red dot sight, cleaning kit, suppressor, user manual, magazine pouch. Includes Multitool knife souvenir from Switzerland. Place of origin: SAN Swiss Arms AG - Schaffhausen, Neuhausen am Rheinfall, Switzerland.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSG550GR">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, a C-MORE red dot sight, cleaning kit, suppressor, user manual, magazine pouch. Includes Multitool knife souvenir from Switzerland. Place of origin: SAN Swiss Arms AG - Schaffhausen, Neuhausen am Rheinfall, Switzerland.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSIG552">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, laser sight, a C-MORE red dot sight, cleaning kit, suppressor, user manual, magazine pouch. Includes Multitool knife souvenir from Switzerland. Place of origin: SAN Swiss Arms AG - Schaffhausen, Neuhausen am Rheinfall, Switzerland.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSIG552GR">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, laser sight, a C-MORE red dot sight, cleaning kit, suppressor, user manual, magazine pouch. Includes Multitool knife souvenir from Switzerland. Place of origin: SAN Swiss Arms AG - Schaffhausen, Neuhausen am Rheinfall, Switzerland.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSIG553">The SG 553 has increased reliability over the SG 552. The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, laser sight, a C-MORE red dot sight, cleaning kit, suppressor, user manual, magazine pouch. Includes Multitool knife souvenir from Switzerland. Place of origin: SAN Swiss Arms AG - Schaffhausen, Neuhausen am Rheinfall, Switzerland.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSIG553GR">The SG 553 has increased reliability over the SG 552. The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of JHP ammunition, laser sight, a C-MORE red dot sight, cleaning kit, suppressor, user manual, magazine pouch. Includes Multitool knife souvenir from Switzerland. Place of origin: SAN Swiss Arms AG - Schaffhausen, Neuhausen am Rheinfall, Switzerland.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSG751">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 120 rounds of JHP ammunition, laser sight, compatible bayonet, 4x ACOG scope, cleaning kit, suppressor, user manual, magazine pouch. Includes Multitool knife souvenir from Switzerland. Place of origin: SAN Swiss Arms AG - Schaffhausen, Neuhausen am Rheinfall, Switzerland.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGType89">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 150 rounds of M193 ammunition, compatible bayonet, a Truglo red dot sight, cleaning kit, suppressor and load bearing equipment. Place of origin: Howa Machinery Company Ltd - Kiyosu, Aichi, Japan.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGType64">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 120 rounds of M80 ammunition, compatible bayonet, cleaning kit, suppressor and load bearing equipment. Place of origin: Howa Machinery Company Ltd - Kiyosu, Aichi, Japan.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGSC2010">Shipment of one SC2010 Assault Rifle, four spare magazines, 120 Rounds of M80-Ammo, Rifle Case, ACOG-Optic and M3 Weaponlight. Place of Origin: Disenos Casanave S.A. - Lima, Peru.</str>
	
	<!-- SNIPERS -->
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGM82A1">A brand new Barett M82A1 Anti-Material-Rifle with two Magazines, special 12.7x99 Ammo, Leupold MK4 Scope and Aluminum Case for Transport. Place of Origin: Murfreesboro, TN, USA.</str>
	
	<!-- LMGS -->
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGULTIMAX">Ultimax MK 5 Tactical LMG with a Optic, Drum Mags, Weapon Light, Laser and other Accessoires. Place of Origin: Singapore.</str>

    <str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGFNMAG">Package of one FN MAG 7.62x51mm GPMG, 500 M80 NATO Rounds, two Box-Mags, ELCAN-Sight, MG-Case, Cleaning Kit and Pouches. Place of Origin: Herstal, Belgium.</str>


	<!-- CAIXAS DE ARMAS -->
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGAK103">This package consists of a crate containing 5 AK-103 7.62x39 Assault Rifles, 10 spare magazines, user manual, 5 cleaning kits, 600 rounds of ammunition and load bearing equipment. Place of Origin: CAVIM (C.A. Venezolana de Industrias Militares) - Caracas, Venezuela.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGMD97Box">This package consists of a crate containing 5 Imbel MD-97L 5.56 Assault Rifles, 10 spare magazines 5 cleaning kits, 600 rounds of ammunition and load bearing equipment. Place of Origin: IMBEL (Industria de Material Belico do Brasil) - Minas Gerais, Brazil.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGM964CIVBox">This package consists of a crate containing 5 Imbel M964 MD2 semi automatic 7.62x51 Battle Rifles, 10 spare magazines 5 cleaning kits, 600 rounds of ammunition and load bearing equipment. Place of Origin: IMBEL (Industria de Material Belico do Brasil) - Minas Gerais, Brazil.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGM964Box">This package consists of a crate containing 5 Imbel M964 select fire 7.62x51 Battle Rifles, 10 spare magazines 5 cleaning kits, 600 rounds of ammunition and load bearing equipment. Place of Origin: IMBEL (Industria de Material Belico do Brasil) - Minas Gerais, Brazil.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGType56Box">This package consists of a crate containing 5 Norinco Type 56 7.62x39 Assault Rifles, 10 spare magazines 5 cleaning kits, 600 rounds of ammunition and load bearing equipment. Place of Origin: Norinco (China North Industries Corporation) - Xicheng District, Beijing, China.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGNorincoCQBox">This package consists of a crate containing 5 Norinco CQ 5.56x45 Assault Rifles, 10 spare magazines 5 cleaning kits, 600 rounds of ammunition and load bearing equipment. Place of Origin: Norinco (China North Industries Corporation) - Xicheng District, Beijing, China.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGGalilBox">This package consists of a crate containing 5 Galil 5.56 Assault Rifles, 10 spare magazines, user manual, 5 cleaning kits, 600 rounds of ammunition and load bearing equipment. Place of Origin: INDUMIL (Industria Militar de Colombia) - Bogota, Colombia.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGGalilACEBox">This package consists of a crate containing 5 Galil ACE 5.56 Assault Rifles, 10 spare magazines, 5 cleaning kits, 600 rounds of ammunition and load bearing equipment. Place of Origin: INDUMIL (Industria Militar de Colombia) - Bogota, Colombia.</str>

	<!-- CAIXAS DE BALAS -->
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45CBCShipment">The kit consist of 5 spare magazine, 2 suppressors, a laser aiming module and a tactical flashlight. Place of Origin: Porto Alegre, Brazil - Forjas Taurus S.A..</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x39Shipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x39mm M43 Armor Piercing ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Xicheng District, Beijing, China - Norinco.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x39ShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x39mm M43 Armor Piercing ammunition, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Xicheng District, Beijing, China - Norinco.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51NorincoShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm FMJ ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Xicheng District, Beijing, China - Norinco.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51NorincoShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm M43 Armor Piercing ammunition, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Xicheng District, Beijing, China - Norinco.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45Shipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Xicheng District, Beijing, China - Norinco.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45ShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Xicheng District, Beijing, China - Norinco.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45AlgeiraShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Algeira.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45AlgeiraShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Algeira.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG9mmAlgeiraShipment">Shipment with 2500 rounds of 9mm, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Algeira.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG9mmAlgeiraShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 2500 rounds of 9mm, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Algeira.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51AlgeiraShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Algeira.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51AlgeiraShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Algeira.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45CBCShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm M193 FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45CBCShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm M193 FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG9mmCBCShipment">Shipment with 2500 rounds of 9mm FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG9mmCBCShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 2500 rounds of 9mm FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45CBCAPShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm M995 Armor Piercing, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45CBCAPShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm M995 Armor Piercing, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51CBCShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm M80 FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51CBCShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm M80 rounds, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51CBCAPShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm M993 Armor Piercing, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51CBCAPShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm M993 Armor Piercing, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51FMShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Fray Luis Beltran, Santa Fe, Argentina - Fabrica Militar Fray Luis Beltran.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51FMShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm rounds, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Fray Luis Beltran, Santa Fe, Argentina - Fabrica Militar Fray Luis Beltran.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG9mmFMShipment">Shipment with 2500 rounds of 9mm FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Fray Luis Beltran, Santa Fe, Argentina - Fabrica Militar Fray Luis Beltran.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG9mmFMShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 2500 rounds of 9mm rounds, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Fray Luis Beltran, Santa Fe, Argentina - Fabrica Militar Fray Luis Beltran.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x39PalShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x39mm Palinero surplus ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x39PalShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x39mm Palinero surplus ammunition, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x54PalShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x54mmR Palinero surplus ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x54PalShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x54mmR Palinero surplus ammunition, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG545x39Shipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.45x39mm Palinero surplus ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG545x39ShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.45x39mm Palinero surplus ammunition, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>

	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGGrenadeF1Box">Shipment with six Soviet-designed Cold-War-Era F1 Hand Grenades, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>

	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGGrenadeM67Box">Shipment with three M67 Hand Grenades, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Joliet, IL, USA.</str>

	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGGrenadeM61Box">Shipment with four M61 Hand Grenades, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Ramat haScharon, Israel.</str>

	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGGrenadeRGD5Box">Shipment with four RGD-5 Hand Grenades, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>

	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGGrenadeRGNBox">Shipment with four RGN Hand Grenades, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Vinnytsia, Ukraine.</str>

	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGGrenadeRGOBox">Shipment with five RGO Hand Grenades, requires use of tools to open, included in this package is a bonus free of charge Swiss Pocket Knife suitable to opening it. Place of Origin: Military District Far East, Russia.</str>

	

</strings>