<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<strings>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGType89">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 120 rounds of M193 ammunition, compatible bayonet, a Truglo red dot sight, cleaning kit, suppressor and load bearing equipment.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGType89Fast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 120 rounds of M193 ammunition, compatible bayonet, a Truglo red dot sight, cleaning kit, suppressor and load bearing equipment.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGType64">The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 120 rounds of M80 ammunition, compatible bayonet, cleaning kit, suppressor and load bearing equipment.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEGType64Fast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. The kit consists of 4 spare magazines, 120 rounds of M80 ammunition, compatible bayonet, cleaning kit, suppressor and load bearing equipment.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45CBCShipment">The kit consist of 5 spare magazine, 2 suppressors, a laser aiming module and a tactical flashlight. Place of Origin: Porto Alegre, Brazil - Forjas Taurus S.A..</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x39Shipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x39mm M43 Armor Piercing ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Xicheng District, Beijing, China - Norinco.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x39ShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x39mm M43 Armor Piercing ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Xicheng District, Beijing, China - Norinco.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51NorincoShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm FMJ ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Xicheng District, Beijing, China - Norinco.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51NorincoShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm M43 Armor Piercing ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Xicheng District, Beijing, China - Norinco.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45Shipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Xicheng District, Beijing, China - Norinco.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45ShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Xicheng District, Beijing, China - Norinco.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45AlgeiraShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Algeira.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45AlgeiraShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Algeira.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG9mmAlgeiraShipment">Shipment with 2500 rounds of 9mm, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Algeira.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG9mmAlgeiraShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 2500 rounds of 9mm, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Algeira.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51AlgeiraShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Algeira.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51AlgeiraShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Algeira.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45CBCShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm M193 FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45CBCShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm M193 FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG9mmCBCShipment">Shipment with 2500 rounds of 9mm FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG9mmCBCShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 2500 rounds of 9mm FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45CBCAPShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm M995 Armor Piercing, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG556x45CBCAPShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.56x45mm M995 Armor Piercing, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51CBCShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm M80 FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51CBCShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm M80 rounds, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51CBCAPShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm M993 Armor Piercing, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51CBCAPShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm M993 Armor Piercing, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Ribeirao Pires, Sao Paulo, Brazil - CBC.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51FMShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Fray Luis Beltran, Santa Fe, Argentina - Fabrica Militar Fray Luis Beltran.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x51FMShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x51mm rounds, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Fray Luis Beltran, Santa Fe, Argentina - Fabrica Militar Fray Luis Beltran.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG9mmFMShipment">Shipment with 2500 rounds of 9mm FMJ rounds, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Fray Luis Beltran, Santa Fe, Argentina - Fabrica Militar Fray Luis Beltran.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG9mmFMShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 2500 rounds of 9mm rounds, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Fray Luis Beltran, Santa Fe, Argentina - Fabrica Militar Fray Luis Beltran.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x39PalShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x39mm Palinero surplus ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x39PalShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x39mm Palinero surplus ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x54PalShipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x54mmR Palinero surplus ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG762x54PalShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 7.62x54mmR Palinero surplus ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>
	
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG545x39Shipment">Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.45x39mm Palinero surplus ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which are NOT included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>
	<str id="lang/cfg/weaponorder/order/GEG545x39ShipmentFast">Express delivery, pay a higher fee for a quicker delivery. Shipment with 3000 rounds of 5.45x39mm Palinero surplus ammunition, requires use of tools to open, which ARE included in the delivery. Place of Origin: Palinero.</str>
	
	

</strings>